talbots.com 2018-10-19

# Talbots Customer Service- Privacy Policy

To view our Terms of Use click _here_

**Revised: February 12, 2018. This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 12, 2018.**

This Privacy Policy applies to information that may be collected by or on behalf of The Talbots, Inc. ("Talbots", "we", "us"). Talbots values your trust and respects your privacy. We are committed to responsibly protecting your personal information and using your personal information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

By doing business with or interacting with Talbots in the manner described in this Privacy Policy at any time after the Effective Date, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the application of this Privacy Policy to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described.

### Table of Contents

  * Who Do I Contact With Questions Or Concerns?
  * What Personal Information Does Talbots Collect?
  * Why Does Talbots Collect Personal Information?
  * How Does Talbots Collect Personal Information?
  * How Does Talbots Use The Personal Information That It Collects?
  * Does Talbots Share My Personal Information?
  * How Does Talbots Secure My Personal Information?
  * How Can I Review, Update And Correct My Personal Information?
  * What are My Choices About Behavioral Advertising?
  * How Does Talbots Respect My Choices About My Personal Information?
  * Mobile Device Data Collection
  * Links to Other, Third Party Web Sites
  * Children's Privacy
  * California Privacy Rights
  * Contact Information
  * Changes To Talbots' Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us. Talbots postal address is: Talbots, One Talbots Drive, Hingham, MA 02043. You can contact us by telephone at 1-800-TALBOTS (1-800-825-2687), FAX 1-800-438-9443, or by email at [customer.service@talbots.com](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com). Canadian customers should direct their inquiries to our Canadian Privacy Officer, who can be contacted at the address and phone number listed above or by email at [privacy.officer@talbots.com](mailto:privacy.officer@talbots.com).

### What Personal Information Does Talbots Collect?

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual and includes information that can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Such information may include your: 

  * Name
  * Postal or shipping & handling address
  * Telephone number
  * E-mail address
  * Payment information (like credit or debit card number and billing address)
  * Birthday and addresses listed in your myTalbots account address book
  * Feedback and comments
  * Shopping preferences
  * Purchasing Behaviors

### Why Does Talbots Collect Personal Information? 

We collect your personal information in order to: 

  * process and ship any purchase you make
  * to administer our business (e.g., to make web site improvements)
  * to enable you to participate in our loyalty programs
  * to enable you to create and maintain wish lists
  * to communicate with you, including by electronic means, about special offers, promotions and other marketing programs that may be of interest to you
  * to allow the creation and administration of contests
  * to be able to contact you by electronic communications or otherwise, if necessary, about the products you have purchased from us
  * to provide you with an enhanced customer experience
  * to provide you with easy access to our products and services, with a focus on the items that may be of particular interest to you

Your personal information also allows us to communicate with you, including by electronic means, about special offers, promotions and other marketing programs that may be of interest to you. If you should no longer wish to receive such marketing communications by electronic mail, kindly advise us and we will cease sending them to you. For your convenience, we may include an unsubscribe mechanism in such electronic communications to permit you to manage how you receive such communications. We also collect personal information for purposes of fraud protection.

### How Does Talbots Collect Personal Information? 

#### Information You Provide

As a general matter, you may browse in our stores and on our websites without submitting personal information to Talbots. However, in order to provide the services and products you request we ask for certain personal information when you shop with Talbots through any shopping channel (online, in stores or by telephone) or when you register for an online account.

We may also collect personal information from online accounts, surveys, reviews, contests, loyalty programs, wish lists, emails you send us or when you request a catalog or sign up for marketing e-mails. We may maintain a record of products you are interested in and purchases you have made in our stores, by phone or online.

Additionally, when you contact customer service, we may ask you to provide or confirm personal information so that we can better serve you.

#### Information Automatically Collected

There are circumstances in which we may automatically receive and collect personal information from you. The most common of these circumstances are described below and include:  

  * Cookies
  * Pixel tags
  * From joint marketing partners, unrelated third parties and from our affiliated brands

Talbots.com and related online properties may leverage Adobe Analytics, Google Analytics, and similar analytics and/or internet-based advertising tools in this process. You can learn more about how Google uses data when you use their partners' sites or apps here: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>. Talbots may use the following features in conjunction with Google Analytics for Display Advertisers: Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

Talbots may combine personal information provided by you with non-personal information collected from other sources, such as cookies, pixel tags or outside sources, in order to provide you with a superior customer experience. 

#### Cookies

Like many online retailers, Talbots uses 'cookies', small data files stored on your computer's web browser, or other passive means of data collection. Cookies are used to personalize your visit, remember your preferences, help place your order or to enhance your shopping experience and online browsing. We, or vendors with whom we contract, may also use technologies, such as cookies, to provide you with personalized advertising tailored to your interests. For more information about your choices regarding this type of advertising, please see the section titled "What are My Choices About Behavioral Advertising," below. You can adjust your web browser to accept or reject cookies, however, if you disable all cookies, some features of the site may not work as intended. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](https://dtmc.talbots.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2830&cname=Talbots&cmagic=073806&clogo=2830.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

#### Pixel tags

We use 'pixel tags' (small graphic images also called web beacons or clear gifs) or similar technologies to monitor the effectiveness of our web site and our marketing and advertising campaigns. We track information in the aggregate about your visit like the web pages you view, the links you click on, and the time you spend on a page. We use this information to track the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns so we can learn how to best deliver your customer experience. We also track our e-mail campaigns in the aggregate to determine whether recipients opened the e-mail and what links they clicked on.

#### Outside sources 

We may periodically collect personal information about you from joint marketing partners and unrelated third parties, which is combined with other personal information we collect from you.

Also, to improve our marketing and the content of our website we collect aggregate, non-personal data like Internet Service Provider's domain name, the referring URL and the web pages and information you access on our site. We use this information to analyze visitors' behavior in the aggregate to improve our web site and your shopping experience.

Anonymous information collected through passive means such as cookies or pixel tags may also be collected on our website and used in connection with targeted advertising campaigns on Talbots behalf by third-party advertising companies. For more information about your choices regarding interest-based advertising, please see the section titled "What are My Choices About Behavioral Advertising," below. 

### How Does Talbots Use The Personal Information That It Collects? 

Talbots uses your personal information to provide you with a superior customer experience at our stores and on our websites and to administer our business. For example, the personal information we collect may be used to: 

  * Fulfill your order and communicate with you about it;
  * Contact you about products, services, events, promotions or contests we think you may be interested in, except where prohibited by law;
  * Enhance your shopping experience, improve the content and navigation of our website, and customize content, layout or offers; and
  * Protect the security of our website and to analyze trends and statistics.

#### Information collected from visitors outside Canada and the United States 

If you are visiting Talbots from outside Canada or the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your personal information may be transferred, stored and processed within Canada and/or the United States. The data protection or privacy laws in Canada or the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country.

**By doing business or interacting with Talbots, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to facilities located in Canada and/or the United States and other facility locations selected by Talbots, and understand that such information will be stored and processed in accordance with U.S. and/or Canadian law, as applicable.**

### Does Talbots Share My Personal Information? 

Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is important to Talbots. When appropriate, Talbots shares personal information among our family of companies and other third parties to help provide you with better service and information about our products and services that we believe would be of interest to you, except where prohibited by law.

We share select information with the service providers we use to help manage our business for things like: 

  * Order processing
  * Payment processing
  * Fulfilling orders
  * Market research
  * Advertising and promotion of Talbots products
  * Fulfilling promotions and managing contests
  * Name and address verification
  * Customer information
  * E-mail management
  * Print and letter shops
  * Service bureaus
  * To host our website, data storage or ad servers 

Notwithstanding any other provision, we partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising to you. We may share personal information you have provided to us, such as your name, postal address, email address, or device ID to these partners for this purpose, however, our partners are prohibited from using this personal information for their direct marketing purposes. Our partners may place or recognize a cookie on your computer, device, or directly in our emails/communications, and may collect non-personal information by utilizing pixel tags embedded on our website or in our emails to you. Our partners may link the non-personal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. For example, our partners may deliver an ad to you in your web browser based on a purchase you made in a retail store, or they may send a personalized marketing email to you based on the fact that you visited a particular website. You can read more about your choices regarding behavioral and interest-based marketing in the section below. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we determine, in our judgment, that it is necessary to (a) comply with the law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request; (b) enforce the terms of any of our polices; or (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Talbots, its employees or customers. This may include assistance in fraud protection or investigation.

We could also sell, rent, disclose or transfer your personal information to a successor entity in the event of a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate changes respecting Talbots or our affiliated companies.

From time to time we may share your personal information with marketing partner companies whose products or services we feel you might be interested in, except where prohibited by law. We may also share your name, address and purchasing behavior with cooperative databases that we may participate in or with our list rental fulfillment vendors, except where prohibited by law.

**If you prefer not to have your personal information shared with these organizations, cooperative databases or screened partners for their direct marketing use, please contact us by telephone at 1-800-TALBOTS (1-800-825-2687), FAX 1-800-438-9443, or by email at[customer.service@talbots.com](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com). Or you may write us at Talbots, One Talbots Drive, Hingham, MA 02043. Canadian customers should direct such requests to our Canadian Privacy Officer, who can be contacted at the address and phone number listed above or by email [privacy.officer@talbots.com.](mailto:privacy.officer@talbots.com) In order for Talbots to confirm your identity and ensure your wishes are honored, requests sent to Talbots email addresses must be sent using the email account to which the request pertains.**

### How Does Talbots Secure My Personal Information? 

Talbots undertakes appropriate security measures to help to safeguard your personal information and seek to prevent unauthorized access and disclosure.

Talbots undertakes measures to ensure that shopping with us is a safe and enjoyable experience for our valued customers. We use a variety of current technologies, managerial safeguards, protocols and processes as we work to protect the security and privacy of your personal information. We want you to feel confident whenever you visit us in our stores, on our website or otherwise. 

### How Can I Review, Update And Correct My Personal Information? 

You may view, update and correct your personal information by accessing your myTalbots account, entering your email address and password and making the changes there. You may also cancel your myTalbots account. To request changes to your personal information, please contact us by telephone at 1-800-825-2687, FAX 1-800-438-9443, or by email at [customer.service@talbots.com](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com). Or you may write us at Talbots, One Talbots Drive, Hingham, MA 02043. It may take up to 10 business days for your requested changes to take place

#### Canadian customers

Canadian customers can also request access to their personal information stored by Talbots by contacting us and we will inform you about what type of personal information we have on record or in our control, how it is used and to whom it may have been disclosed, provide you with access to your personal information so you can review and verify the accuracy and completeness and request changes to the personal information and make any necessary updates to your personal information. There are instances where applicable laws or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide some or all of the personal information that we hold about you. In addition, the personal information may have been destroyed, erased or made anonymous in accordance with our record retention obligations and practices. If we do not provide you with access to your personal information, we will endeavor to inform you of the reasons why, subject to any legal or regulatory restrictions. 

Canadian customers should direct their inquiries to our Canadian Privacy Officer, who can be contacted at the address and phone number listed above or by email at [privacy.officer@talbots.com](mailto:privacy.officer@talbots.com). 

### What are My Choices About Behavioral Advertising? 

Like many retailers, Talbots contracts with third-parties to serve or send advertisements on our behalf. Advertising companies will typically collect anonymous information about a user's browsing activity, including the websites visited and the products viewed, and will then use that information to serve or send targeted advertisements. These targeted advertisements such as campaigns through Google AdWords including remarketing, interesting category marketing, similar audience campaigns, interest-based advertising, and demographic and location targeting. Some customers prefer not to receive this type of advertising. 

Some websites have "do not track" features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform. We do not currently respond to those signals. However, many of Talbots marketing partners are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, or the Digital Advertising Alliance, and have agreed to honor consumers' opt-out preferences submitted through those organizations' websites. To learn more about your choices regarding this type of data collection or to opt-out of interest-based advertising by members of the NAI or the DAA, please visit the choices websites of the NAI <https://www.aboutads.info/choices> or the DAA <https://www.aboutads.info/choices>. On a mobile device, you may visit the DAA's AppChoices website here: <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>. You also may locate Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) You can find more information about how to opt-out of Adobe Analytics here: [http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html.](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html)

### How Does Talbots Respect My Choices About My Personal Information? 

By providing personal information to Talbots, including through Talbots.com, you acknowledge and agree that you fully understand and consent to the collection, use, retention and disclosure of such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**If you wish to be removed from our marketing emails, calling or postal mailing lists please contact us by telephone at 1-800-TALBOTS (1-800-825-2687), FAX 1-800-438-9443, or by e-mail at[customer.service@talbots.com](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com) or you may write to us at Talbots, One Talbots Drive, Hingham, MA 02043. Canadian customers should direct their inquiries to the Canadian Privacy Officer, who can be contacted at the address and phone number listed above or by email at [privacy.officer@talbots.com](mailto:privacy.officer@talbots.com). In addition you may remove yourself from our marketing e-mail list by clicking [here](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com), or on the unsubscribe link that is at the bottom of each marketing email. Please include your name and mailing address in any correspondence.**

For calling list removal, it may take up to 30 days to process your request.

For postal mailing list removal, it may take up to 6-8 weeks to process your request as our customer personal information is collected in advance due to printing schedules.

Please note that even if you opt out of receiving marketing communications, you may continue to receive e-mails, mailings or calls relating to order confirmations and/or other transaction-related communications.

### Mobile Device Data Collection 

In (and near) our stores we may use our Wi-Fi or Bluetooth networks to track the location of your mobile device to measure traffic and shopping patterns, which we believe will help to provide with better customer service to you. Specifically, we may record the unique identifier (called the "MAC address") that is broadcast by your mobile device within (or near) our stores along with the time, the signal strength, and the location of the observing sensor. We do not store the payload of wireless network packets (meaning the data that your mobile device is sending or receiving over Talbot's Wi-Fi or Bluetooth network). The information we collect will not be linked to you personally, but will include the MAC address of your mobile device. Unless you explicitly opt into a related service from Talbots, Talbots will not use this collected data to identify you by name.

Information collection of broadcast information from your mobile device within (or near) our store will be facilitated by our service provider RetailNext, Inc. Both Talbots and RetailNext will have access to the collected information, which will be used by each in accordance with their respective privacy policies. RetailNext's privacy policy can be viewed at [https://privacy.retailnext.net](https://privacy.retailnext.net/), We will not share with other third parties broadcast information collected from your mobile device within (or near) our stores. 

You may, at any time, choose to opt out of having your mobile device counted in statistics provided by the RetailNext platform by going to [https://privacy.retailnext.net](https://privacy.retailnext.net/) to opt out. You may also choose to opt out of having your mobile device tracked within our stores by turning off your device or turning off your Wi-Fi and Bluetooth services on your mobile device.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this policy, we may preserve or disclose mobile device broadcast information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, or legal request or to protect the safety, property, or rights of Talbots or others.

### Links to Other, Third Party Web Sites 

Occasionally we may provide links on our website to third party sites we think you may be interested in. These sites are independent from Talbots and have their own separate privacy policies. Whenever you click on links on Talbots website that take you to a third party website, you will be subject to the third party's privacy policies, and not Talbots. We recommend that you review their privacy polices before you visit these sites. 

### Children's Privacy 

Talbots website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit any personal information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for an online account. Should we learn that someone under the age of 13 has provided any personal information to or on Talbots website, we will remove that information as soon as possible.

### California Privacy Rights 

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, Talbots customers living in the State of California can request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please contact us by telephone at 1-800-TALBOTS (1-800-825-2687), FAX 1-800-438-9443, or by email at [customer.service@talbots.com](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com) or you may write to us at Talbots, One Talbots Drive, Hingham, MA 02043.

### Contact Information

Talbots is a member of the Direct Marketing Association (DMA) and complies with its standards for use of your personal information in a manner that respects your wishes. Upon request we offer registered visitors the ability to correct inaccuracies in their contact information. Please contact us by telephone at 1-800-TALBOTS (1-800-825-2687), FAX 1-800-438-9443, or by email at [customer.service@talbots.com](mailto:customer.service@talbots.com). Or you may write us at Talbots, One Talbots Drive, Hingham, MA 02043. Canadian customers should direct their inquiries to our Canadian Privacy Officer, who can be contacted at the address and phone number listed above or by email at [privacy.officer@talbots.com](mailto:privacy.officer@talbots.com).  

### Changes To Talbots' Privacy Policy

Talbots reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes will be posted on our website. We encourage you to check Talbots Privacy Policy when you visit our website
